你非常幸运 你知道吗
Pretty lucky, you know that?
幸运 我媳妇开枪射我
Lucky? My wife shot me.
只在你的肩膀上有一点皮肉伤
Well, it's above your shoulder and it's barely a flesh wound.
再往下一英尺 你可能就没命了
An inch down, it would've stopped your heart,
所以 是的 你很幸运
so, yeah, you're lucky.
好吧 怪我媳妇没瞄准
Well, here's to my wife's bad aim.
从现场来看 你俩
From the looks of this place, you two had
来了场非常激烈的争吵 是吧
a pretty heated argument, huh?
我媳妇是个好人 但是她酗酒
My wife's a good person with a bad drinking problem
更糟糕的是容易吃醋
and even worse jealous streak.
特别是什么事情激起了她的嫉妒心理
Anything in particular happen to activate that jealous streak?
以为酒店柜台后面的
Thought the girl behind the
女孩在和我调情
counter at the bodega was flirting with me.
好吧
Okay.
一天前 是地铁上的某个女人
Day before, it was some woman on the subway.
再往前一天 是接待我们的女服务员
Day before that, it was our waitress.
我要继续说吗
Should I keep going?
不用 她很容易吃醋
Okay, she's got a jealous streak.
我们知道了 她现在在哪里
We get it. Where is she now?
我打911的时候她跑出去了
She ran out the second I called 911.
我试图阻止她 但是
I tried to stop her, but...
你觉得她可能去哪儿
Any idea where she might go?
如我所说 她酗酒
Like I said, she's got a drinking problem.
她可能去哪个有酒卖的地方呢
Any particular watering hole she'd go to?
任何有酒的地方
Any hole with water.
- 嘿 有空吗 - 没有
- Hey, got a minute? - Nope.
哦 好吧
Oh, okay.
但对你 我会抽个空 怎么了
But for you, I will make one. What's going on?
他们让我负责科斯特洛的抢劫案
Well, they got me on this Costello robbery.
坏人抢劫了一位老妇人
Bad guy robbed an old lady on her way home
在她从杂货店回家的路上
from the grocery store.
- 等等 他们没告诉你吗 - 告诉我啥
- Wait, didn't they tell you? - Tell me what?
我正把这件案子降等为行为不当
I'm knocking that down to a misdemeanor petty larceny.
什么 为什么
What? Why?
因为我还有其他500件案子排在它前面
Because I've got 500 other cases ahead of it
需要占用我们的时间和资源
that need our time and resources.
- 排在老妇人被抢案之前吗 - 不
- Ahead of an old lady getting robbed? - No.
我的意思是 根本就不算一件案子
What I mean is, there is no case.
他们互相反驳 各执一词
It's her word against his.
没有武器 没有监控录像
There's no weapon, there's no surveillance footage.
他是第一次犯罪
He's a first-time offender.
在我还没开口说
The judge will give me the stink eye before I even get,
"早上好 尊敬的法官大人"之前 他就会满目鄙夷
"Good morning, Your Honor," Out of my mouth.
- 所以你打算结案了是吗 - 是的 我职责所在
- So you're gonna cut bait? - Yeah, that's my job.
那是你新的职责
That's your new job.
你对我的新职位有异议吗
Do you have a problem with my new position?
只是以前的艾琳会把现在的艾琳关到铁笼子里
Only that the old Erin would've clotheslined this new Erin
来彻查这个案子
in a steel cage match to see this case through.
新来的这个雷根比他老爸还白莲花
This new guy Reagan's more Boy Scout than NYPD.
因为我没带手电筒就训我
Gave me a rip 'cause I wasn't wearing my flashlight
还是大白天的
during the day.
- 就是 - 警长对我们就跟对待
- Exactly. - Sarge is handing out CD's
在天主教学校犯了错误的学生一样
like demerits back in Catholic school.
今天早上经过他的时候 我小声说
I pass him this morning, I say under my breath,
"你脑子有屎还是仅仅是很高兴见到我"
"Is that a stick up your butt or you just happy to see me?"
我现在换到夜班了
Now I'm working midnights.
当你老爹是局长时你就会这样子
What you get when your old man's the Commissioner.
他不是第一个自以为可以改变2-9分局的警长
He's not the first boss who thought he could change the 2-9.
等待时机吧 亲们
Bide your time, boys.
我敢说也就一个月
I give it about a month before he's begging Daddy
他就会求他老爹把他调离这儿
for a transfer out of here.
你真的以为我会那么说
You really think I'm gonna say that?
我开始觉得可能不会
I'm starting to think maybe not?
绝对不会
Definitely not.
也许你可以那么说
Perhaps you could say that,
虽然你感激伊斯坦布尔人的提议
while you appreciate Istanbul's offer,
但你现在还不能接受
you are unable to accept
警察局长的邀请
the police chief's invitation at present.
或者就说你不舒服
Or just say that you're under the weather.
你为什么不实话实说
Why don't you just tell the truth?
伊斯坦布尔的警方演练让你
That Istanbul's police practices make you long
对过去那种戒严令产生了憧憬
for good old-fashioned martial law.
盖瑞特呢
Where's Garrett?
他堵在贝德福德-斯泰森特社区到市政厅的路上了
He's held up at the Bed-Stuy community outreach town hall.
当你和伊斯坦布尔人交谈时你会说什么
What are you gonna say when you talk to Istanbul?
我不知道
I don't know.
我即兴表演的时候状态最好
I'm at my best when I just wing it.
但是头儿 我敢打赌这个家伙
But boss? I'm betting this guy's seen
已经身经百战
every duck and heard every excuse ever invented.
好吧 也许我能想出一个新点子
Well, maybe I can come up with a new one.
局长 红色代码
Commissioner, this is a code red.
有一个可信威胁
We have a credible threat.
请远离窗户
Please step away from the window.
雷根局长 请确认您的身份
Commissioner Reagan, if you would confirm your identity.
欢迎来到勇者地堡
Welcome to Bravo Bunker.
勇者地堡
Bravo Bunker?
- 谢谢你 长官 - 局长
- Thank you, Chief. - Commissioner.
- 我能问一下我们在那里吗 - 勇者地堡
- Can I ask where we are? - Bravo Bunker.
是啊 我们知道这个称呼了 这是个什么地方
Yeah, we got the name. What is this place?
这是我们无处可去时的藏身之地
This is where we go when everywhere else is a no-go.
已经到这一步了吗
And has that happened?
局长 您的电脑已连网
Commissioner, your computer is online
您的安全电话已确认并可以使用
and your secure phone is confirmed and ready for use.
谢谢你 警督 我们该怎么办
Thank you, Inspector. How'd we do?
记下工作日的最佳镜头
Record best time for the weekday scenario.
很好 干得漂亮同志们 放松
Good. Well done, everyone. At ease.
头儿 我绝对放松不了
Boss, I'm definitely not at ease.
所以我们没有受到攻击
So we're not under attack?
没有 这只是一次演习
No, this was just a drill,
但如果有攻击
but had there been an attack,
你会遵循同样的程序
you would've followed the same procedure.
这个地方不是闹着玩的
This place is no joke.
这里可以全面运行
We're fully operational here.
我们在总局做的任何事情 都可以在这里做
Pretty much anything we do at 1PP, we can do here.
除了订披萨
Except order pizza in.
你们要带着这个卡片
In order to access
才能进入这里
this building, you'll need this card.
请随身携带
Keep it on you at all times.
你们甚至不能
And you can't even tell
告诉你们的神父这个地方的存在
your priest about this place.
除了你在这里见到的人外
If you don't see them in this room,
都不能透露对其余人出去
you can't talk to them about it.
我能问一下为什么我们会突然出现在名单上吗
Why are we on the list all of a sudden, may I ask?
不
No.
不 我们不在名单上吗
No, we're not on the list?
不 你不能问
No, you may not ask.
翻译 冰熊
多
啦
A
没有
梦
翻译 叶知晚
北
极熊
小
白
翻译 向野
Sh
ey
la
校对 素时
A
u
s
l
e
y
总校 蓝白色的甜栗子
特
效
Shey
l
a
压制 蓝白色的甜栗子
总监
蓝
白
色
的
甜
栗
子
警
察
世
家
第九季     第三集
脑力游戏
Mind Games
本字幕由蓝血字幕组
译制
仅供交流学习 严禁用于任何商业盈利行为
有什么消息吗
Anything?
- 妻子叫克拉拉·海耶斯 - 嗯哼
- Wife's name is Clara Hayes. - Uh-huh.
她走了 消失了 没有网络活动
She's gone. Vanished. No online activity.
蓝血字幕组
没有发现车牌信息 什么痕迹都没有
No hits on the license plate readers. Nothing.
她会露面的
She'll show up.
为什么你看起来没那么担心
Why don't you seem more worried?
因为她最后一次自动取款机交易在三天前
Because her last ATM transaction was three days ago.
蓝血字幕组
她取了100美元
She withdrew $100.
花完的时候 她就不得不
When that runs out, she's gonna have to
再次使用那张卡或者信用卡
use the card again or her credit card,
那个时候
and when that happens,
这个电话就会响起来
this phone's gonna ring.
但你听见他丈夫说的了 她是个酒鬼
But you heard her husband, she's a drunk.
万一她在某个小巷里昏过去怎么办
What if she's passed out in some alley somewhere?
如果她在哪个小巷昏倒了
If she's passed out in an alley somewhere,
她最后还是会醒过来 那时候
she's gonna wake up eventually, and when she does,
她会需要一些食物 或者 更有可能再来一杯
she's gonna want some food or, most likely, another drink.
我认为我们应该检查一下急诊室
I think we should check the emergency rooms.
查过了
Already did.
无家可归者的收容所呢
And the homeless shelters?
我是雷根
Reagan.
在 什么信息
Yeah, what do you got?
Edward Joseph酒店
Yeah, the Edward Joseph Hotel over there
在皇后区大桥那儿 我知道了
by the Queensboro Bridge, I know it.
你逗我呢
You're kidding me.
谢谢你
Thank you.
她刚在屋顶酒吧结了一单
She just opened up a tab at a rooftop bar.
我喜欢屋顶酒吧
I love rooftop bars.
我也是 我们一起狂欢去
Me, too. Let's crash the party.
抱歉我迟到了 我...
Sorry I'm late, I...
是的
That's right.
开始工作了
Start the paperwork.
科斯特洛太太
Mrs. Costello.
呃 我晚点再打给你
Eh, let me get back to you.
进来吧 进来 我给你腾个座
Come in, come in. Here, let me make some room.
我很抱歉打扰你
I'm sorry to bother you.
完全没有
It's no bother at all.
你心情好点了吗
You're still upset?
我不明白 我被袭击了
I just don't understand. I was assaulted.
我被抢劫了 警方在
I was robbed. The police
我的头上看到了肿块
saw the bump on my head,
但是你告诉我
and then you're telling me
你打算把我的案子归类为什么都没有
you're knocking my case down to nothing.
你瞧 实话实说 科斯特洛太太
Look, I-I'll be honest with you, Mrs. Costello,
我也和你感受相同
I-I feel exactly the same way as you.
- 所以你为什么要这样做 - 我无能为力
-So then why are you doing it? -My hands are tied.
地检署办公室决定哪些案子会起诉
The D.A.'s office decides which cases they're gonna prosecute.
这样可不对 安东尼
It's not right, Anthony.
相信我 我知道的
Believe me, I know.
你要是继续这样附和我 我要敲你了
You keep agreeing with me, I'm gonna bop you on the head.
至少反对我一下
At least fight with me.
这 来吧 你可以打我的手臂
Here, come on, you can punch me on the arm.
- 来吧 - 嗷
- Come on. - Oh.
现在好些了吗
There, feel better?
没有
Nope.
你瞧，我对此很抱歉 科斯特洛太太 真的
Look, I-I'm sorry, Mrs. Costello, I really am.
我不知道当一个女士被枪指着
I don't know what the world is coming to
这座城市却无动于衷的时候
when a woman can be held at gunpoint
这个世界会变成什么样
and there's not a damn thing the city can do about it.
再次申明 我
Again, I-I'm...
等等 你说你被枪指着
Wait, did you say held up at gunpoint?
是的
That's right.
但是在警察的报告里
There's no mention of a gun
完全没有提到枪
in the police report.
他们应该提到的
Well, there should've been.
那个小杂碎举着枪指着我的肋骨
That little rat held it right here at my ribs.
那你告诉警察没有
And you told the cops?
是的 我告诉了
Yes, I did.
不知道怎么的报告里没有提到
Well, somehow it didn't make it into the report.
科斯特洛太太 这可是能翻盘的
Mrs. Costello, this changes everything.
- 真的吗 - 是的
- It does? - Yeah.
哦 真好
Uh, hell yeah.
现在他犯了B级重罪
Now we got him on a B violent felony.
- 这很棒吧 - 非常
- Is that good? - Very.
嘿 这是
Hi, this is
艾伯特马克警探 我打电话来是关于一个犯人
Detective ABETEMARCO, I called you about that prisoner.
不要释放他
Do not release him.
没有人告诉你你穿这身警长制服超帅吗
Anyone ever tell you you look great in stripes?
抱歉让你久等了
Sorry to keep you waiting.
呃 有什么事吗
Um, what-what brings you down here anyway?
我也很高兴见到你 宝贝
Nice to see you, too, sweetheart.
我只是想说我没想到你会来
I just mean that I wasn't expecting you.
因为这就是一个惊喜呀
That's because it was a surprise.
- 惊喜 - 哦 谢谢
- Surprise! - Oh, thank you.
- 来自Di Palo的奶酪茄子 - 哇
- Eggplant Parmesan hero from Di Palo's. - Whoa.
味道和原来一样
Taste of the old neighborhood.
你真好
That's really nice of you.
- 一切都还好吗 - 当然
- Is everything okay? - Sure.
但是我在这你表现得并不是很开心
'Cause you don't seem okay with me being here.
- 我很好 - 真的吗
- I'm fine. - Really?
因为我绝对有一种
'Cause I'm definitely getting
不好的的感觉
a "Not fine" Vibe.
工作罢了 埃迪
Just working, Eddie.
那么在这工作怎样
So how's it going down here?
你不会没有机会休息一下吧
You haven't really had a chance to break it down.
还好
Good.
所以这个2-9分局真的像人们说的那样难搞
s the 2-9 really as tough as they all say it is?
呃 很忙 街上有很多坏蛋
Uh, busy. Lot of bad guys on the streets,
比12分局忙多了
much busier than the 12th.
那除了巡逻呢
What about off the streets?
- 什么 - 我是说警局内部呢
- Hm? - In the station house, I mean.
你和其他警察相处的怎样
Are you getting along with Th-the other cops?
- 呃 我现在是警长了 - 对
- Well, I'm a sergeant now. - Right.
- 意味着我和他们不是兄弟了 - 当然 但
- Means I'm not their buddy. - Sure, but...
但是什么
But what?
没什么 你说的没错
Nothing. You were right.
我不该耽误你工作
I should get out of your way. Um...
或许也不能和你吻别 对吧
Probably shouldn't kiss you good-bye, right?
我晚点再找你 感谢你的午餐
I'll check in with you later. Thank you for lunch.
- 你要求见我 警长 - 进来
- You wanted to see me, Sarge? - Please.
克拉拉 无论你想象的有多坏
Clara, whatever you think is so bad,
我保证不是那样的
I promise you is not so bad.
我射中了我的丈夫
I shot my husband.
我之前想要杀掉唯一一个爱我的人
I tried to kill the only person who ever loved me.
唯一的一个看到我优点的男人
The only man who ever saw any good in me.
我有办法
I got an idea.
- 你有手机吗 - 当然
- You got your phone? - Yeah.
我要你给我发短信
I want you to text me.
你想我发什么
What do you want me to say?
我醉了
I'm a drunk.
我没有用
I am worthless.
抓住我的手
Take my hand
我们进来谈吧
and let's talk about this inside.
不 我不傻 一旦我进来 你们会因为蓄意谋杀
No, I'm not stupid. If I go with you, you'll take to jail
而抓我进监狱的
for attempted murder.
发了吗
You send it?
快点 快 快
Come on, come on, come on.
好了
Sent it.
告诉理查德 我很抱歉
Tell Richard I'm sorry.
告诉他 他是对的
Tell him he was right.
我从来都配不上他
I was never worthy of him.
克拉拉 不要那样
Clara! Don't do it!
克拉拉 看着我
Clara! Look at me.
看着我 克拉拉
Look at me, Clara.
这罪不该死
It doesn't have to be a death sentence.
警督
Lieutenant.
我能试试吗
Can I try something?
你知道什么 丹尼
What do you got, Danny?
嘿 克拉拉 我这有个人你想和他说话
Hey, Clara? I have someone here that wants to speak to you.
克拉拉
Clara?
雷根警探
Detective Reagan.
我当时和和你丈夫在现场
I was first on the scene with your husband.
他怎样了 他还好吗
How is he? Is he okay?
理查德他很好 好吧 仅仅是伤到肌肉了
Richard's fine. Okay? He's got a flesh wound,
他能下床 过不了多久他就痊愈了
he's on his feet, he'll be like new in no time.
- 他恨我 -不 他没有
- He hates me. - No, he doesn't.
他发给我这条消息 你瞧
He sent me with a message. Look.
你瞧 拜托 看看这
Look, come on, look at this.
他说的
That's his words.
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
警探...告诉我的妻子
我爱她 我也原谅了她
你一定尽全力去救她
没有她我也活不下去
他发给你的吗
He sent you that?
他原谅你了 好吧
He forgives you, okay?
他希望你能安全 他爱你
He wants you to be safe. He loves you.
现在让我来接你下来
Now let me get you down from there,
去见他 他可以当面告诉你
get you back to him, he can tell you those words himself.
可以吗
All right?
行吗
Okay?
好
Yeah.
行
All right.
- 我很抱歉 - 嗯 没关系的
- I'm sorry. - Okay. It's okay. Okay.
没关系的
It's all right.
好了 好了
All right, all right.
- 有明确的嫌疑人 - 是的
- We got a positive ID... - Yep.
- 自枪手的坦白 - 嗯
- ...A confession from the shooter. - Mm-hmm.
有武器
You've got the weapon,
弹道显示就是这把枪
and ballistics confirms it's the gun.
对的
Yep.
打扰一下 你对我哥哥丹尼·雷根干了什么
I'm sorry, what have you done with my brother Danny Reagan?
你总爱开玩笑
Always with the jokes.
怪我咯 你总是带着证据不全或是凭直觉的案子
Well, can you blame me? You usually come in here
来到我这里
with a half-baked case and a hunch.
但是今天你带着证据齐全的案子来了
Today, you're walking in with a royal flush.
不 今天 我带着疑惑
No, today, I walked in
来到这里的
with a pair of twos and three stragglers.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
呃 有些事情感觉不对
Eh, something's not right about it.
太简单了
It's too easy.
你简直不可理喻
You are impossible.
- 不 我是认真的 - 让我猜猜
- No, I'm serious. - Let me guess.
- 又是你的直觉 - 不
- It's your gut. - No,
这不是我的直觉 好吗
it's not my gut, okay?
这很难解释清楚 就是有什么地方不对
I can't explain it, it just doesn't pass the smell test.
[有什么地方闻着不对劲]
那就把鼻子塞住 这已经是一击大灌篮了
Then plug your nose, because this is a slam dunk.
你的被告自己表明
You have a defendant indicating
她会认罪的
She's gonna plead guilty.
别这样 别让她这么做
No, no. Do not let her do that.
好了 到此为止 出去
Okay. That's enough. Get out.
不 说真的
No, I'm dead serious, okay?
至少不要是马上 可以吗
At least not yet, anyway.
有什么东西不对劲
Something isn't right.
对 那就是你
Yeah, it's... it's you.
走吧
Now go.
走
Go!
即使我不想要你帮忙 你还是和我唱反调
Even when I don't want your help, you won't help.
你开什么玩笑
You're kidding me.
大新闻啊
This is great news.
安东尼
Anthony.
晚上请你大餐
Steak dinner on me.
时间地点你定
You name the time and the place...
搞什么鬼
What the hell are you doing?
这也是我想问你的
That's the exact question I want to ask you.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
为什么我收到电子邮件 询问我们什么时候出席
Why am I getting e-mails asking when we're presenting
科斯特洛抢劫案的陪审
- the Costello robbery case to the grand jury?
- 哦 对 这是好消息啊 - 我特别指出过
- Yeah, yeah, look, uh, it's good news. - I specifically said
我们在那个案子上指控行为不当
we were offering a misdemeanor on that case.
是的 但又发生了一些事
Yeah, but something's come up.
现在是一件很不错的案子了
It's a much better case now.
- 是吗 - 千真万确
- Oh, is that right? - A hundred percent.
有意思 我可没在这间办公室里看到
Interesting. Because when I look around this office, I don't see
一个法律学位
a law degree anywhere.
哇
Wow.
你现在开始来这一套了
Now you're gonna play like that, huh?
对 我来我自己这一套 安东尼
Yeah, I'm gonna play any way I want, Anthony.
- 小心说话 艾琳 - 不 你才是
- Careful Erin. - No, you be careful.
现在撤案
Now drop it.
什么
What?
你听见我说的了
You heard me.
我不能那么做
I can't do that.
你好 这里是助理检察官雷根
Yes, this is A.D.A. Reagan.
你不能就这样...
- You did not just do...
- 案子里有一把枪 艾琳 - 什么枪
- There was a gun, Erin. - What gun?
罪犯用一把弹径9厘米的枪
Uh, t-the perp stuck a-a nine
顶着科斯特洛夫人的肋骨
right in old lady Costello's ribs.
那份警方报告里可没提过有枪 安东尼
There is no mention of a gun on that police report, Anthony.
那份文件跟别的混在一起了
There was a mix-up with the paperwork,
我们已经整理好了文件 也找到了那把枪
We got it sorted out. We also got the gun.
我们有可能放走这个犯了B级重罪的混蛋
We could put this punk away on a B felony.
你之前怎么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me that?
- 我有尝试过 - 不 你没有
- I've been trying... - No, you haven't.
至少不够努力
Not hard enough.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
现在把那份文件拿给我
I want that paperwork on my desk now.
最好是准确无误 分毫不差
- Every "I" Better be dotted, every "T" Better be crossed.
收到 长官
Yes, ma'am.
贝兹
Baez.
你知道吗 你的预感一点用都没有 雷根
You know, your hunch sucks, Reagan.
理查德·海耶斯的信用卡记录一切正常
There is nothing unusual with Richard Hayes's credit cards,
社交媒体上也没什么问题
nothing unusual on his social media.
什么都没有
Nothing, Nada.
一定在什么地方有问题
Yeah, but there's something there.
是什么让你坚持认为他有问题
What makes you so sure there's something going on with him?
我就是知道 感觉不对
I just know it. Something doesn't feel right.
从证据来看什么问题都没有
Well, everything in the evidence says it feels great.
你错了 雷根
You're wrong, Reagan.
不 这次不会错的 贝兹
No, I'm not wrong this time, Baez.
尽管很难接受
I know it's tough to swallow,
但是伟大的丹尼·雷根也会有出错的时候
but even the great Danny Reagan can be wrong sometimes.
说的是
Yes.
我是会出错 在某个极为罕见的时候
I can be wrong, on that rare occasion.
但不是这次
However, this isn't that time.
电话记录 信用卡记录 银行记录
Phone records, credit cards, bank records,
社交媒体 工作档案
social media, employee file.
每一项都非常干净
Every single one of them checks out squeaky clean.
除了这个
Every single one except this one.
这是什么
What the hell is that?
我跟踪了那个心碎的丈夫理查德·海耶斯
I followed the heartbroken husband Richard Hayes,
直到他扑进他女朋友充满爱与温暖的怀中
right into the loving and waiting arms of his girlfriend.
- 她是谁 - 不知道
- Who is she? - I don't know.
她叫什么
Well, does she have a name?
也不知道
Don't know that, either.
不过我猜海耶斯夫人可能知道
But I suspect Mrs. Hayes might.
现在我要把发言权交给盖瑞特
And now I am going to hand it off to Garrett.
还有什么事儿吗 我饿死了
What else you got? I'm starving.
最后一件
Last item.
我跟伊斯坦布尔方面聊过了
I spoke to Istanbul.
- 是吗 - 是的 我还告诉他们
- You did? - And I told them
你非常期待与纳迪尔主席
you were very excited to meet with Chief Nadir
在你巡回竞选时候的会面
during your swing through.
你同意了晚宴会谈吗
You agreed to a sit-down?
而你的首要任务是
And that top on your list
带着随行人员与媒体记者去
was visiting their jails, with retinue
参观他们的监狱
... and press in tow,
以向世界展示他们的人权
to show the world just how much
得到了多大的提升
they'd improved on human rights.
结果呢
And the upshot was?
他们会再联系我们
They'd get back to us.
没下文了吗
As in, don't hold your breath?
翻译人员说完就没了
Even in translation.
非常好
That's very good.
我的临场发挥也不会比这更好了
I don't think I could've winged it any better.
你要临场发挥
You were gonna wing it?
- 对啊 - 对
- Yeah. - Oh, yeah.
他都是一切都准备好了 当...
He was all set to when the, uh...
当什么
- When the what?
没 没事
Nothing. It was nothing.
听起来可不像是没事
It doesn't sound like nothing.
有事发生了
Something came up.
所以还是有事
So it was something.
呃
Uh...
耸肩 这就是你的回应吗
Shrugs? That's all you got?
只是演习
It was just an exercise.
像是 一个消防演习
Like, a fire drill.
像是一个消防演习还是一个消防演习
- Like a fire drill, or a fire drill?
像
Like.
这就是为什么我来的时候 你们谁都不在的原因吗
- Is that why none of you were here when I came by?
对 可能是
Yeah, probably.
所以你们去哪里了
So where'd you guys go?
警务工作
Police business.
警务
Police?
对
Yes.
那我干的是什么事务呢
And what kind of business am I in?
卖床上用品的吗
Mattresses and bedding?
我现在只能告诉你这么多
That's all I can tell you right now.
明白了
Copy that.
我饿死了
I'm starving.
我气饱了
I'm not.
不好意思
Excuse me.
这是很长时间以来
This is the first time
我们第一次一起吃早饭
getting to eat breakfast together in a long time.
- 晚餐 - 哦对 忘了
- Dinner. - Right, forgot.
谢谢你在睡觉之前愿意见我
And thank you for meeting me before going to sleep.
你会持续多久的夜间工作啊
Any idea how much longer you'll be working midnights?
直到坏人们都遵守银行开闭时间
Till the bad guys start keeping banker hours.
温斯顿跟莫拉莱斯昨天来12分局
So, Winston and Morales came by the 12th yesterday
来拿他们剩下的东西
to pick up the rest of their stuff.
- 嗯 怎么 - 他们说2-9分局
- Mm-hmm? - They said the 2-9
非常地狱模式
is pretty hardcore.
对 纽约最忙的地方 他们知道的
Yeah, busiest house in the city. They knew that coming in.
对 但我猜
Well, yeah, but I think
他们还是有些被惊讶到了
they were a little surprised, you know?
那里一些警察的工作态度
The attitude of some of the cops there?
噢 他们会习惯这些的
Oh, they'll get their sea legs.
你知道的 需要一段时间来适应新的环境
You know, it takes a while to get used to a new place.
我打赌适应新头儿
It's even tougher for a new place
比新环境要难的多
to adjust to a new boss, I bet.
埃迪 你想说什么吗
Is there something on your mind, Eddie?
没有
No.
你能再说一遍吗
Can you say that again?
我觉得我像在跟人肉测谎仪约会
I swear, it's like dating a human lie detector.
比那更惨 你和人肉测谎仪订婚了
Worse. You're engaged to a human lie detector.
这并不好笑
It is not funny.
你不如就告诉我你到底在想什么
Why don't you just tell me what's really on your mind?
没什么
It's nothing.
你就这么不愿意谈谈吗
That's why you're so reluctant to discuss it?
好了 那天我过去找你
Okay, fine. The other day I came by to see you
有几个警察在前台聊天
and there were some cops hanging out front,
说起你的时候 他们嘴里没好话
and they were talking smack about you.
他们叫什么名字 警徽号呢
What are their names and shield numbers?
我不知道 但如果我见到他们 我能认出来
I don't know, but if I saw them, I could pick them out.
我逗你的
I'm kidding.
- 啊 哦 - 我逗你的
- Oh. Oh. - I'm kidding.
埃迪 我们搭档这么多年
Eddie, of all the years that we rode together,
我们俩说过我们警长的坏话吗
did you and I ever bitch about our sergeant?
说过 但那不一样
Well, yeah, but that's different.
每个人都讨厌他们的上司
Everyone hates their boss.
如今我当上司了 你也该习惯这事
And I'm a boss now, something you got to get used to.
但我不明白 他为什么不在这里
But I-I don't understand why he's not here,
因为你说过 他为什么没和你一起来
'cause you told-- why isn't he here with you?
你说过他很想我
'Cause you said that he missed me.
- 是的 - 他跟你说
- Yeah. - He told you that...
他跟你说他原谅我了
he told you that he forgives me.
没错
Yes.
我相信他很快会来看你的
I'm sure he's gonna visit you soon.
但同时
But in the meantime,
我们希望你能帮我们一个忙
we need you to help us with something, okay?
他就这么干 他总这么干
He does this, he does this.
他嘴里说着一套
You know, he, he'll s-say one thing,
实际上又做着另一套
and then he does the other,
我就成了那个疯子
and I'm somehow the crazy one.
克拉拉 我们想给你看点东西
Clara, we want to show you something.
听着 他有时让我
Like, he'll-he'll tell me
去做一件事 我就做了
to do something, and I'll do it.
我做了之后 他又说我没这么做
I'll do it, and then he'll tell me that I didn't do it.
- 好了 克拉拉 - 或是我跟别人说了什么
- Okay, Clara... - Or I'll talk to someone,
- 克拉拉 - 我跟他说了
- Clara. - and I'll tell him something, and then
但他又坚持说我并没告诉他 但我说了 真的
he'll insist that I never told him, and I did, I did.
克拉拉
Clara.
我需要你集中精力 好吗
I need you to focus in right now. Okay?
好的
Yeah.
可以吗
Can you do that?
好的 可以 抱歉
Yeah. Yeah, sorry.
这是什么
What is it?
你认识这个女人吗
Do you know this woman?
呃
Um...
认识 这是麦凯布医生
Yes. This is Dr. McCabe.
麦凯布医生 好的
Dr. McCabe. Okay.
你丈夫也认识麦凯布医生吗
Does your husband know Dr. McCabe, also?
我们都认识 她是我们的婚姻咨询师
Uh, we both do. She's our couples therapist.
婚姻
Couples...
咨询师
therapist.
好的
Okay.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
麦凯布医生在这栋楼里
Dr. McCabe's building is over here.
你一会儿就知道了
You'll see.
你在街上做什么
What are you doing in the street?
我在找这个
I'm looking for this.
就是这个
Right here.
"警察大人 请不要开罚单"
"Police, please don't ticket."
纽约市里的门卫都会这招
Every doorman in the city makes this play.
好吧 但是为什么
Okay, but why?
打扰一下 警官
Excuse me. Officer.
- 我就在这里 - 请叫我警探
- I'm right here. - Yeah, it's Detective.
标志牌说了这里任何时间都不许停车
And the sign says no standing any time.
我知道 警探 我很抱歉
I know, Detective, and I'm sorry.
- 嗯哼 - 最近的车库在六个街区外
- Mm-hmm. - The next garage is six blocks away
一天要一百刀
and a hundred dollars a day.
这可不是我们的问题
Yeah, well, that's not our problem.
- 打电话喊拖车来 - 不 不要
- Call for a tow, please? - Oh, no.
不要拖车 求你了
No, no, please.
我跟你说 我们帮你的忙 你也要帮我们的
Tell you what, we help you, you help us.
好了 你认识这个女人
Okay. Do you know this woman,
- 麦凯布医生吗 - 是的 我认识她
- Dr. McCabe? - Yeah, I know her.
她叫卡密尔·麦凯布 住在3C
That's Camille McCabe, 3C.
但是医生吗 她可不是什么医生
But doctor? She ain't no doctor.
她不是在她的公寓里
She doesn't run a couples therapy business
做婚姻咨询的吗
out of her apartment?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about with that.
她是位教授 但不是婚姻咨询师
She's a professor, or something. No couples therapist.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
过得愉快
Have a good day.
好了 好了
All right, all right.
你们人真好 但这真的不是什么事儿
It's very nice of you guys, but it was no big deal.
干得好 安东尼
No, it was good work, Anthony.
谢谢 我真的很感谢
Thank you very much. I really appreciate it.
一会儿见
I'll see you guys in a bit, huh?
干得好 安东尼
Great work, Anthony.
我就想告诉你
Hey, uh, I just wanted to let you know
科斯特洛抢劫案已经起诉了
we got an indictment on the Costello robbery case.
你真的觉得这间办公室里
Do you really think there's anything
有什么事情你能比我先知道吗
that happens in this office that you know about before me?
好的 也是 我就想说声谢谢
Right, of course, uh, I just wanted to say thanks.
不 你在这里 是想要我跟你说谢谢
No, what you were here hoping was that I would say thanks,
但这是不可能的
which is not gonna happen,
所以你可以出去了
so you can be on your merry way.
我不明白 这场诉讼很成功
I don't get it. We got a good indictment.
你为什么这么不高兴
What are you so pissed about?
你让我在所有人面前像个傻子一样
You made me look like an idiot in front of everyone.
抱歉 亲爱的 这是你自找的
I'm sorry, sweetheart, you did that all on your own.
你已经让我很不高兴了
You are already in the doghouse.
你真的想让我发火吗
You really want to end up in the pound?
你 是你一脸怒气的走进我办公室
Look, y-you came into my office a-all hot,
打断我的话 冲我又叫又喊
hanging up on people, screaming and yelling.
你违背了我的直接命令
You disobeyed a direct order.
我没有违背命令 我发现了新的信息
I didn't disobey, I just came upon new information.
而你就继续去做了
And then you proceeded to move on it
却没有知会我或办公室里任何人
without clearing it with me or this office.
你不能这么做
You don't get to do that.
事态进展飞快
Things were moving a hundred miles an hour.
我没有这个时间
I didn't have time.
实话说 我都没这么想过
I honestly didn't even think about it.
你该这么想的
Well, maybe you should have.
艾琳 这样的事情你我都一起
Come on, Erin, you and I have done this kind of thing
做了千百次了
a thousand times together.
现在不一样了
It's different now.
为什么
Well, why?
- 因为你现在是老大了吗 - 是的
- 'Cause you're the boss? - Yeah.
没错
That's right.
你让我在所有职员面前表现得像个混蛋
You let me make an ass of myself in front of the entire staff.
你连一句话都不让我说
You wouldn't let me get a word in.
而且
And-and,
实话说 我真的没看到他们
to be honest, I didn't even see them all there.
安东尼 你要和他们共事
Anthony, you have to work with them.
我要领导他们
I need to lead them.
如果他们不尊重我 我就做不到
I can't do that
而多亏了你 我失去了他们的尊重
without their respect, which I lost, thanks to you.
还是不明白你怎么让学校
Still don't understand how you got the college
就这么把她的电脑给了你
to just give you her computer.
我天生英俊帅气
My chiseled good looks.
我用催眠术说服他们的
My powers of hypnotic persuasion.
好了 我和院长说卡密尔·麦凯布
Okay. When I told the dean that Camille McCabe
涉及一起警方调查
was the subject of a police investigation,
他说这台电脑并不属于她
he said the computer didn't belong to her,
它属于纽约州政府
it belonged to the state of New York.
所以他就把电脑给我了
So he gave it to me.
我想院长不想因此
I guess the dean doesn't want to run afoul
失去州政府资金
of that sweet state funding.
听起来没错
Sounds right to me.
查到什么了吗
Anything yet?
没什么突出的 不过 这个有点奇怪
No real red flags, but... well, this is a little weird.
什么
What is?
你看过那部老电影《煤气灯下》吗
You ever see that old movie Gaslight?
煤气 没有
Gas-- no.
她看过
Well, she has.
还看过很多遍
Quite a bit, it seems.
- 你看见这些网站了吗 - 嗯哼
- You see all these websites? - Mm-hmm.
这些网址要么是留言板
Each of them is either
要么是电影粉丝的博客
a message board about the movie or a fan blog.
有些甚至是关于
Some of them are even psychiatric papers
动态精神病学的论文
written about the dynamic.
好吧 到底是什么呢
Okay, well, what the hell is it?
在电影里
Well, in the movie,
丈夫基本上把妻子逼疯了
the husband basically drives the wife insane.
就像是心理战
It's like psychological warfare.
随着时间推移 丈夫逐渐让妻子
And over time, he slowly convinces her
相信她所想的一切都是错的或是幻觉
that everything she thinks is wrong or her imagination.
就是海耶斯夫妇的情况
That's what you think this is,
你是这样想的吗 心里蒙蔽
with the Hayes couple, uh, gaslighting?
听起来很像她前几天
Well, it sounds a lot like what she was saying to us
对我们说的话 对吧
the other day, right?
- 听起来像胡说八道 - 拜托
- It sounds like nonsense. - Come on.
你也相信一下我的直觉 我都信你的了
Listen to my hunch. I went with yours.
怎么了
What?
我觉得可能我们俩的直觉都是对的
I think both our hunches might be right.
这儿不是奥古斯塔 好吗
You realize this isn't Augusta, right?
好吧
Okay!
太厉害了
That was amazing.
怎么做到的
How'd you do that?
做什么了
Do what?
你打算告诉我 咱们来这儿的原因吗
So you want to tell me why we're back here?
你为什么总是这么多疑
Why are you always so suspicious?
职业病
Occupational hazard.
我就是觉得会好玩
I just thought it'd be fun.
所以碰巧选在了我向你求婚的地方
So the fact that I proposed to you here is just a coincidence?
我想调到2-9分局
I want to transfer to the 2-9.
什么
What?
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
但这是你当初的想法
But it was your idea.
以前是 你拒绝了
Was, and then you turned it down.
那我又想接受
Well, I'm turning it up.
- 不行 - 为什么
- The answer is no. - Why?
因为你觉得分局的警察不喜欢我
Because you think the cops at the 2-9 don't like me,
你认为我有了公关危机
you think I have a public relations problem
你想来做我的私人公关
and you want to come over and be my personal DCPI.
不是这样的
That is not true.
好吧 是有点关系
Okay, fine, it's a little true.
一开始是因为这个 但并不是真正的原因
It started out that way, but that's not the real reason why.
你干什么...
What are you...
好吧
Fine.
好吧 真正的原因是这个
Fine. Here's the real reason.
我们的结婚誓言
Our vows.
我不希望誓言只是我们
Yeah. I don't want them to just mean something
婚礼上的一项
on our wedding day.
我希望今天 明天
I want them to mean something today
以后的每一天都让誓言有意义
and tomorrow and every day after that.
我会永远支持你
I will always have your back.
如果你落在后面 我会等你
If you fall behind, I'll wait up.
我们在一起的每一天 我会赢得你的尊重 并给予你尊重
I'll earn your respect, and pay you respect, every day we have.
我会成为你的侦察兵 你的守卫 你的骑兵
I'll be your scout, your night watchman, your cavalry.
你的医生 你的牧师 在你我的二人军队里
Your medic, your chaplain in our army of two.
- 不撤退 不投降 - 不投降
- No retreat. No surrender. - No surrender.
你可以依靠我
You can count on me.
你也可以依靠我
你的意见呢
And your two cents?
你说了算
Oh, totally your call.
我知道 但我在征求你的意见
I know that, but I am asking for your input.
你认为最好的就行
Whatever you think is best.
话是没错 但我做的决定
Yes, and the way I make that determination
其中囊括我向你
is a process that includes me
征求你的意见
soliciting your opinion.
我意见有用吗 这是警务工作
Why would my opinion matter? It's police business.
终于说出来了
And there it is.
反正你说什么都是对的
Now, when you're right, you're right.
而且你说对了 我不是警察
And you're right, I am not a cop.
别说了
Oh, cut it out.
我非常有信心能够在属于警务工作特定事务上
I am confident that I could advise you on certain matters
这是办公室 不是过家家
It's an office, not a sandbox.
给你提供建议
that pertain to police business,
不过由于有一堵死板的警察之墙
caused by the hidebound big blue wall
把我从警务工作方面的事务隔开
that police business is conducted behind...
- 盖瑞特 别再说了 - 虽然...
- Garrett, please cut it out. - ...the jams that lack
有失管理透明度 但我不是警察
of transparency causes, but I am not a cop,
因此 我需要回避
so I recuse myself on matters
这些专业领域问题
requiring that expertise.
行吧 只能来硬的了
Okay. We'll do it the hard way.
麦凯布医生
Dr. McCabe?
Dr. McCabe.
我们是雷根和贝兹警探
Detectives Reagan and Baez.
有事吗
Yes?
你是麦凯布医生吧
You are Dr. McCabe, right?
卡密尔·麦凯布 博士
Camille McCabe, PhD.
这么说 你不是
Mm. So not
婚姻咨询师 卡密尔·麦凯布医生
Dr. Camille McCabe, couples therapist, right?
有什么事吗 警探们
Can I help you detectives with something?
是的 的确有事
Yeah, actually, you can.
你认识理查德·海耶斯多久了
How long have you known Richard Hayes?
谁
Who?
和你激情舌吻的男的
The guy with his tongue down your throat.
我不确定
I don't know.
有一年吧
Uh, a year?
那你们二人对海耶斯太太
And how long have you and Richard Hayes
进行心理蒙蔽多久了
been gaslighting Mrs. Hayes?
你说什么
E-Excuse me?
自第一次讨论起
We had been seeing each other
我们俩差不多有一年了
for about a year when we first discussed it.
你们讨论如何蒙蔽理查德的妻子克拉拉吗
Discuss your plan to gaslight Richard's wife Clara.
理查德很多次
Richard tried
都试图离开她 她就是不同意
to leave her many times. She would simply refuse.
所以你们决定把她逼疯
And that's why you decided to drive her mad?
不是逼疯 是让人产生困惑
It doesn't make you insane, it just confuses you.
是谁的主意
Whose idea was it?
我为了备课做的一些
I was doing some research on the topic
相关研究 引起了理查德的兴趣
for one of my lectures, and it caught Richard's eye.
他让我继续钻研
He asked me to drill down on it.
你照做了
And you did.
结果没起作用
And when that didn't work,
你决定再加把劲 假扮
you decided to double down, and take on the role
理查德和克拉拉的夫妻治疗师
of a phony couples therapist for Richard and Clara?
理查德坚称她就要崩溃了
Richard insisted she was close to breaking.
觉得只要来一点推动
He just thought she needed a little nudge.
"推动" 指用氯仿将她迷晕
"Nudge" Being drugging her with chloroform
再布置一场谋杀未遂
and staging an attempted murder.
都是理查德的主意
Hey, that was all Richard.
跟我没有关系
I had nothing to do with that.
当我发现理查德让我研究氯仿的影响
When I found out the reason that Richard wanted me
的原因时候
to research the effects of chloroform,
我跟他说他疯了
I told him he was crazy.
我说我不想参与此事了
I said I wanted nothing to do with it.
但你没有报警
But you didn't call the police.
没
No.
我是该报警的
But I should have.
我真的应该报警
I absolutely should have.
你愿意在法庭上
Would you be willing to testify in court
作证吗
to all of this?
当然 绝对愿意
Absolutely. A hundred percent.
理查德应当为自己的行为付出代价
Richard should pay for what he did.
当然
Absolutely.
绝对愿意
A hundred percent.
理查德应当为自己的行为付出代价
Richard should pay for what he did.
胡说 彻头彻尾的胡说八道
This is garbage. Complete and utter nonsense.
都是她的主意
This was all her idea.
- 各执一词 - 没错
- He said, she said. - Yep.
她先招的 所以你觉得呢
And she said first, so guess what?
她的说法更有力
She's the grand prize winner.
- 她在说谎 - 嗯哼
- Well, she's lying. - Mm.
伪造枪击是她的主意
It was her idea to fake the shooting.
她主张让一切看起来是
Her idea to make it look like
- 克拉拉枪击了我 - 我信你啊
- Clara shot me. - I'm sure it was.
我没说谎 都是她的计划
I'm not lying. This was all her plan.
她当时也在现场
She was there, too.
- 再说一遍 - 真的
- Say again. - It's true.
她躲在厨房里
She was in the kitchen, hiding.
是她把氯仿倒在酒里的
She's the one that slipped chloroform into her drink.
也是她开的枪
Hell, she's the one who actually shot me
在克拉拉昏迷后
after Clara passed out.
听起来你有点像在孤注一掷啊
Sounds like you're throwing a little bit of a Hail Mary,
你觉得呢 理查德
don't you think, Richard?
千真万确
It's the God's honest truth.
- 各执一词 - 没错
- He said, she said. - Yeah.
除非你能证明 快点
Only matters what you can prove. Come on.
- 快点 起来 - 等等
- Come on, get up. - Wait, wait, wait.
我能证明 我能
I can prove it. I can.
你打算怎么做 理查德
How you gonna do that, Richard?
- 你打算也迷惑我们 - 不不不
- You gonna gaslight us, too? - No, no, no.
我在客厅安了个针孔摄像头
I've got a nanny cam in the living room.
安在那好让我不在家的时候能监视克拉拉
I put it there to keep an eye on Clara when I wasn't home.
卡密尔不知道它 但是
Camille didn't know about it, but...
但是它应该录下了一切
it had to have recorded everything.
枪击的画面就在里面
The shooting will be on there.
嗯 不错
Hmm. Right.
- 噢 - 看
- Oh... - See?
说过的
Told ya.
好吧 你们太疯狂了 但这是个好消息
Well, you guys are crazy, but this is good news.
- 是吗 - 是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- 它能让我脱困吗 - 能让你妻子脱困
- Does this get me off? - It gets your wife off.
够你和你的女友
And puts you and your girlfriend away
吃上好一壶了
for a very long time.
走 起来 起来
Come on, get up. Get up!
所有警员集合点名
Officers, fall in for roll call.
- 库珀警员 - 到 长官
- Officer Cooper. - Here, sir.
2-9F 这次别忘了填上
2-9 Frank. Don't forget to fill up this time.
- 特德斯科警员 - 到
- Officer Tedesco. - Here.
巡逻后15街
Patrol post 15.
- 扬科警员 - 到 长官
- Officer Janko. - Present, sir.
巡逻后11街
Patrol post 11.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
欢迎来到2-9分局
And welcome to the 2-9.
- 古德曼警员 - 到 长官
- Officer Goldman... - Yes, sir.
巡逻后9街
Patrol post 9...
嘿 艾琳 非常抱歉
Hey, Erin, I'm so sorry.
不 是我的错
No, it's me.
就是因为这个工作 我应该
It's just, it's this job. I should have...
不是你错 我应该闭嘴的
Nonsense. I should have just kept my mouth shut.
我也该听你说的
And I should have listened.
不如我们喝杯马丁尼
What do you say we bury the hatchet
就此和解怎么样
in a couple of martinis?
- 放下芥蒂 重归于好 - 好啊
- Straight up with a twist? - Let's do it.
晚安
Good night.
拜
Bye.
摩尔副局长 请跟我们走
Deputy Commissioner Moore, come with us, please.
什么鬼
What the hell?!
跟我们走就是 长官 没事的
Just come with us, sir. It's okay.
跟我们走 立马 我们走
Come with us, right now, let's go.
接人到这里用了12分4秒
12 minutes and four seconds from pickup.
做得不错
Well done.
就这些 警监
That'll be all, Inspector,
谢谢你
and thank you.
我在哪
Where am I?
勇者地堡
Bravo Bunker.
这个地方在911事件后建造的
This place was created in the wake of 911.
为什么我在这儿
Why am I here?
我们也一直在问自己
We've been asking ourselves the same thing.
是的 老大
Yeah, boss.
我马上就会讲到
I am getting to that.
我以为你们三个
Look, I was assuming that all three of you
会同时在我的办公室里
would be in my office at the same time.
你迟到了 所以你从演习名单中剔除了
You were delayed, so you were deleted from the drill.
是的 我确实感到被剔除了
Yeah, I felt pretty deleted.
我...你说的很对
I-- You made that very clear.
但是当时别无选择
But there wasn't an option.
在这里之外不能提到这个地方
No one talks of this place outside of this place.
这个设施是专门为纽约市警局里
This facility was designed for only the most
最不可替代的人准备的
indispensable men and women of the NYPD.
我意识到头衔和职位
I have come to realize that title and rank
不是评判"不可替代"的唯一标准
are not the only things that go into "Indispensable."
你是
You are.
现在我来带你们看看床位
I will now show you your bunks
和厨房
and the kitchen
但是你们最好祈祷
while you say a prayer
我们永远不需要用这些
that we never have to use them.
以圣父
In the name of the Father,
圣子和圣灵的名义
the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
圣父在天 布施恩惠
Our Father, full of grace who arts in heaven,
请赦免我们每日的饮食 凡侵犯我们的
forgive us our daily bread, and blessed is the fruit
必得福乐
of those who trespass against us...
好了 埃迪 埃迪
Okay, Eddie, Eddie,
我必须打断你
I have to stop you there.
认真地 那是什么
Seriously, what was that?
我在祈祷
I was saying grace.
我不知道你刚刚在说什么
I have no idea what you were just saying.
不知道 但它肯定不是祷告
Yeah, but it definitely wasn't grace.
没事 宝贝
It's okay, babe,
我想你有点困惑
I think you just got a little confused.
你刚说的是天父
I think you were saying the Our Father...
提到了一点圣母
With a little Hail Mary thrown in there.
- 然后她又跑回到圣父那边了 - 没错
- And then she circled back to the Our Father again. - Right...
这就像是个非常奇怪的混搭
And then it was just kind of like a super weird mash-up.
没别的意思
It made no sense.
没事的 宝贝 他们只是在调侃
It's okay, babe. They're just busting chops.
是的 它 我只是 我不知道
Yeah, it's-- I just-- I was just, I don't know,
我努力试着融入大家
I was just trying to fit in. I...
我不知道为什么你们所有人都这么刻薄
I don't know why you guys have to all be so mean.
埃迪 他们
Eddie, they were--
你就坐在那 眼睁睁看着他们
You just sat there. You let them.
何必呢 各位
Really, guys?
杰米
Jamie...
好 开心吗
Well... happy?
谁知道她会这么敏感
Who knew she was so sensitive?
谁知道我们这么神经大条
Who knew we were so insensitive?
大概我们习惯彼此了
I guess we're just used to each other.
我最先说的 我应该过去道个歉
I started it. I guess I'll go and apologize.
谢谢各位 很感谢这个温暖的开场
Thanks, guys, I really appreciate the warm welcome.
接下来 刮鼻子吗
What's next, noogies?
- 她走了吗 - 没有
- She leave? - No.
她正在调整心情
She's just getting a grip.
埃迪 我发起的 我错了
Eddie, I-I started it. It was wrong.
确实错了
It was just wrong.
是的 我想这是我们家槽糕的
Yeah, I think it was just our family's
幽默表达方式 我们很抱歉 埃迪
poor attempt at humor. We're-We're sorry, Eddie.
我们随意开玩笑是不对的
Lame of us to go for the easy joke.
更差劲的是
Even lamer of us
拿你的努力来开玩笑
to make fun of the effort you put in.
- 抱歉 - 抱歉
- Sorry. - Sorry.
抱歉
Sorry.
我不知道
I don't know.
我不知道说什么 除了
I don't know what to say, except...
喔 你们太天真了
Wow, you guys are really easy.
- 什么 - 一群笨蛋
- What? - What a bunch of suckers.
流了几滴假眼泪
A few crocodile tears
你们就对我低头了
and you're-and you're just groveling to me.
天哪
Oh, my God.
好吧 所有这一切是个大笑话
Okay, all right, so this is all a big joke.
出来混是要还的
Payback is a bitch.
你是共犯
Oh, so you were in on it?
嗯 受了上周的启蒙之后
Well, after last week's initiation,
我告诉他想让你们
I told him I wanted to give you guys
自食其果
a taste of your own medicine.
所以我们上演了这出
So we cooked this up together.
是的 但是我们家庭的传统是
Yeah, but our family's tradition
- 联合起来开小两口的玩笑 - 没错
is to gang up on the new spouse. - That's right.
而不是反过来
Not the other way around.
好吧 现在我们有了个新的传统
Well, now we got a new family tradition.
干得好
Well done.
非常棒
Bravo.
- 演得很棒 - 做得好
- Well played. - You did good.
给我土豆
Pass the potatoes.
谢谢
Thank you.
太好玩了
It was just so funny.